What happened to the captain?
Now listen up.
If you plan on hurting these ladies,
then you're gonna have to go through me to do it.
Beep-bam!
Beep-boo!
He said I still haven't played my trump card yet.
The last counter-attack by the memory thief who reveals his true colors.
I... I remember.
I'm... me!
I'm me!
I'm myself again!
I remember!
Um...
Excuse me, sir, but aren't you one of our guests?
Yes, I am!
So why am I dressed like I work here?
Hey!
The manager shouldn't be acting like a guest!
Get down to the front desk!
So I... didn't imagine it?
I'm the... I'm really the manager?
Mom! Mom! Where have you been?
I'm so sorry, but I'm here now. Are you okay?
Yes! Our memories have finally returned!
I miss you so much!
Everyone!
Listen!
There's trouble!
Oh, hey, it's Grim!
Don't scare us like that!
It's Grim, my son!
Mom! Mom!
I'm so glad you're safe!
Mom!
Oh, it looks like everyone's memories have finally returned!
That's wonderful!
But...
What do you suppose happened to us?
Everyone!
Please!
Listen to me!
I saw him!
The one who took our memories is in a forest!
Huh?
What?
What's he saying now?
Cut them to pieces, Roro, Noah, Zoro.
That's all.
See?
I knew it!
He's being...
He's being controlled by that thing!
Somebody better do something and fast!
Jeez, it never fails.
Stupid swordsman, he always has to make everything so damn difficult.
Sanchi, be careful!
This will buy me the time I need?
Hoo-yay!
Stay out of my way.
You got that, dumbass cook?
There he is!
Zoro!
Are you guys okay?
Luffy, what the hell? Why'd you do that?
Zoro, did you just call him Luffy?
You got your memory back?
Of course I did.
Then stop looking so creepy.
If it really is back then act like it, okay?
Put a big smile on your face like this!
Hey, stop it!
My head.
Hey, who am I?
Don't make this any more complicated than it already is!
Oh yeah!
Zoro, you got a lot of nerve for what you did.
I don't know why I even bother.
Good.
Now we're all back to normal.
Yep.
Realizing that seahorse horn was the real culprit was brilliant Robin, my love.
What?
So that was it?
Yes, Luffy, that was it.
You were the first one to get your memories back and you didn't notice?
Oh, rude!
At least I'm better than Zoro.
So where'd that thing go anyway?
Did it escape?
Nope.
It's obvious where it is.
Woohoo!
Shhh!
He's right.
It just turned itself blue.
It could have easily gotten away by now.
Did it really think it could hide for-
Bastard!
So you think you can try to manipulate me, huh?
I'll cut you up and serve you for dinner!
Huh.
Really got to him, didn't it?
Ha!
You won't catch me!
Oh yeah?
Just you wait.
Too slow, Jerk!
Jerk!
How about this?
I'm over here!
What the hell?
I'll slice you to shreds!
There!
I've got you!
You won't get away!
You're next, Usopp!
Just wait!
Boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop!
How for my last resort?
Huh?
No!
It can't be!
You're next, Usopp!
Just wait!
Boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop!
How for my last resort?
Huh?
No!
It can't be!
Is that you, Bellamere?
No! It can't be!
Is that you? Bellomere?
Doctor!
Kaya!
Are you feeling better?
Oh!
How are you guys doing?
These people…
I must be from the other's memories.
It's a bird!
You jerks! What a fight! Bring it! I'll kick all of your asses at the same time!
What's going on?
Oh no!
Dammit!
What's it saying now, Chopper?
Thanks to the interference of you meddling pirates, I lost all of the memories I collected from the villagers.
But the delicious memories I've gathered from you are enough for me to transform.
Behold, I will become!
Become what?
I have no idea!
I'm not going to miss this opportunity!
Don't mess it up.
One post-marker!
I will have a bit of the
The End
What the? What's that?
And, uh, and who am I?
And who are you guys?
What the? Who? How?
Huh? Huh?
What? What?
What?
Hey, you, Mr. Drowning Guy.
Do you know who I am?
No, dumbass!
At last. I'm a millennial dragon?
No way!
Awesome! You can tell what that thing's saying!
Wait! It's a talking raccoon dog!
I'm a raccoon dog?
A talking raccoon dog and a dragon?
And some random drowning dude.
What's going on here?
Somehow just looking at that thing is really pissing me off.
Where am I?
What, how, and why is all of this happening?
Strange. What am I doing in this place?
Whoa!
Dragon must ride!
Are you crazy?
Besides, there's no way you can get up there!
I won't know until I...
What kind of freak is he?
What's going on?
My arms and legs get stretched!
This is fun!
Wow, he actually made it up there!
What is his body made out of?
He's a monster!
Oh, what's going on?
Stop bugging around!
Ah!
Looks like that millennial dragon is in some sort of pain!
Let go.
I'm losing the memories.
Memories?
Please?
Bebambo!
You won't stop, will you?
Quit stealing our memories!
You bastard!
Bebambo! Bebambo!
What's he saying?
Chopper!
Chopper?
You mean me?
Yeah, who else would I mean? Right?
I'm finally a Millennial Dragon!
Don't try to stop me!
What did you say?
People's memories aren't yours to take!
If you need some for this transformation,
then go out and make some memories of your own!
Got it!
Silence! I've had enough of you!
I'm going to end it!
Uncle!
Victor!
You wanna fly so bad?
I'll send you flying!
Don't you follow us?
ở trên
Where is the Guinness902nd?
I'm flying!
Ohhhh!
Huh?
He's flying!
Good luck!
What's up?
The Guinness903nd?
No, it wasn't!
Luckily it's not limited easily,
yes, I'm off.
I lost my bad one!
Good luck!
Go ahead!
Wonder what?
What would you admit,
This is a law su décision!
Come on, you'll catch a cold.
I kicked that dragon's ass!
If I remember correctly, aren't millennial dragons hatched?
I mean, don't they come from eggs?
You can't just become one.
Yeah, eating memories won't do anything to change that.
Oh, is that right?
Sure! You probably didn't know about it,
but before we came to the Grand Line,
we saw some with our very own eyes.
Wow!
But never mind that.
I'll bet the villagers are clamoring to see us.
After all, we're the ones who got all of their memories back
and saved the day!
They're gonna treat us like heroes!
Damn straight, and heroes need booze.
Already trying to forget something, are we?
Shut up!
This hero's hoping for a big cash reward!
A big bronze statue! That'd be nice!
I wonder if a lap dance would be out of the question.
Hey, Robin, what would you ask for?
A book, maybe?
Seems right up your alley.
Indeed, it is.
Maybe a book about this island's history.
I knew it!
I want a book, too!
A medical book this thick!
Look! We can see the shoreline!
Greetings, island villagers!
Well, here we are!
Huh?
Whoa!
Hold on!
What are you?
Boo!
They did it!
Everyone, attack!
Ah!
What the heck is going on?
I thought we were supposed to be heroes!
We were!
I'm just as confused as you are!
Hey, Nami, quick!
Where's the waiver?
We can't leave it behind!
It's over this way!
I'll get it!
Hold it!
Stop right there, you filthy pirates!
Memory thieves!
That's you, girl!
Get back here and pay for your room!
What's going on?
They think we took their memories?
So it would seem.
Well, what are we going to do?
What are we going to do?
They think we took their memories?
So it would seem.
Well, we are pirates!
What did you expect?
They've left me no other choice!
Hey!
Hold on!
Stop it!
What kind of pirate would stop
just because someone said to?
You!
Ah!
Thank goodness we made it back!
My Bronze Statue!
I was so close to getting one!
It would have been awesome!
My very own dark cool bronze statue.
Oh man!
I'm glad that's all over!
Losing your memory could sure cause a lot of trouble!
You got that right!
that right, including someone trying to scheme his way into making us his pirate crew.
Come on. Hey, you can still join. What do you say?
There was also a certain simpleton who allowed his mind and body to be taken over by a neurotic
seahorse. What? If you had kept watch like you were supposed to instead of sleeping, then none
of this mess would have happened in the first place, stupid moss head. Shut up. I was tired,
okay? Well, if you're that tired, why don't you sleep forever? Shut it! Enough bickering,
or else you'll be getting another dose of amnesia. Oh, come on. Don't say such mean things, Nummy.
My memories.
If I really had lost all my memories and didn't get them back.
What's wrong, Robin? Huh?
Oh, it's nothing. Just a little tired, that's all. I bet. Poor Robin didn't get to sleep even once
during that entire ordeal. Yeah, that's right. Now, time to start preparing a special recuperative
dinner. What? Dinner? Good idea! Sanji! Dinner!
I said I'd start preparing it. Shut up and wait. Hey, Luffy. Huh? Why weren't you with Zoro when
he found us by the lake? Oh. Well, I kind of got stuck under a boulder Zoro cut. A boulder?
Yeah, to be fair, it was a pretty big boulder.
What's wrong?
On the next, One Piece, Proud Man Silver Fox Foxy!
Ugh!
Him again?